<resources>
    <string name="app_name">JoinGreen</string>
    <string name="AppName">JoinGreen</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="menu_language">Language</string>
    <string name="menu_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_event">Event</string>
    <string name="totalPoints">totalPoints</string>
    <string name="menu_reward">Reward</string>
    <string name="forgotPassword">Forgot Password</string>
    <string name="Logout">LogOut</string>
    <string name="menu_attendance">Attendance</string>
    <string name="attdText">Input Attendance Code Here</string>
    <string name="attdBtn">Attend</string>
    <string name="info">Welcome to Join Green! \n\nIntroduction\nThere is a cycle between humans and environments. Without the environments human cannot be living normally like usual. We found out that Malaysian nowadays less cared about the environmental issues or being a participant in it. In this app, we allowing the user not only joining the events related to environment but also hosting one of it. From that, we hope that more Malaysian no matter what is the age is will be participate in these activities.\n\nProblem\n1.Not having the awareness of participating in the activities of taking care of the environment.\n2.Not having the incentives or motivation to do so \n3.Not feeling one as the society to think that protecting the environment is everyone responsibility \n4.Not knowing any event is being held nearby and unable to participate in the following event.\n5.Having the difficulties to host and attract people to join the event related to 3R \n\nSolution\n1.Sharing the photos to other members in the community to let them know how to do so \n2.Having a point system whenever the user participates in an event, and the points allow the users to redeem the points for rewards \n3.A notification to the user whenever an event related to 3R is being held nearby. \n4.Allowing the user to host an event easily and sharing the news or information to other easily</string>
    <string name="Info">Info</string>
</resources>
